<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hairstyle For You</string>

    <string name="round_short"> THE CUT \n
        A gamine with spiky layers sliced all around the crown like Ginnifer Goodwins chop. \n \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        "If you're going to go short, go short all the way," says legendary celebrity hairstylist Garren. Unlike a jaw-hugging bob,
        this petite pixie downplays roundness in a big way. The choppy pieces up top add height, lengthen your face and emphasize your eyes. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        This length is a cinch to style for straight, wavy and fine hair, but steer clear of it if you have curls-think poodle. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Styling short locks is easy with the Eva NYC Mini Healthy Heat Ceramic Flat Iron. Because of its miniature
        size, you can actually grasp your shortest strands to totally transform your pixie.
    </string>

    <string name="round_medium">
        THE CUT \n
        Show off your features with a choppy, layered bob like Elizabeth Olsen. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        "I think that it also minimizes the face shape when you do go shorter because you don't have all this hair to create more of a round shape," says Olsen of a short bob. "It works here because she's chosen a side-part, so it gives something for the eye to follow."\n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        "When you do a side-part, you want the first piece of your bang to break at your eye," notes Olsen. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Add in beachy waves with T3 Whirl Trio a product we wear by with interchangeable barrels.
    </string>

    <string name="round_long">
        THE CUT \n
        Long, barely there layers that hit at the jawline. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Selena Gomez\'s long, staggered layers are an easy way to make your hair, not your face, seem fuller. A scattering of light
        layers on the bottom keeps volume away from the sides (where you don?t need it) and focuses it near the ends (where you want it). \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        The long layers stop curls from ballooning around your cheeks and prevent fine hair from appearing stringy. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        You, too, can play up your au naturel texture (and avoid damaging heat) by adding a bit of product. We prefer Pantene
        Extra Strong Hold Level 4 for all-day volume and extra hold.
    </string>

    <string name="oval_short">
        THE CUT \n
        A blunt bob with minimal, subtle layers. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        "This face shape is the easiest to carry off any kind of haircut," says Tollo. Go for a strong lob with a little bit of
        face-framing like Diana. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        Pick your go-to, everyday hairstyle based on your natural hair part. That can be your guiding factor. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Because this cut is blunt by nature, play up your natural texture in the styling and stick with a center part. \n
    </string>

    <string name="oval_medium">
        THE CUT \n
        A sleek blowout that hits at the shoulder Ashley Benson\'s. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Ashley Benson\'s layers may look uniform, but the difference is there. The subtle variations in length keep your strands
        from lying flat against your head, which has an elongating effect. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        If your hair is fine, keep uneven pieces around your face so hair looks as full and dense as possible. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        For a high-gloss finish like Benson\'s, we\'re turning to Ouai Hair Oil. \n
    </string>

    <string name="oval_long">
        THE CUT \n
        Long strands paired with a retro texture and sweeping fringe. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Got down-to-there hair? You\'ve probably had it up to here with stylists wanting to lop it off. No more. Side-swept bangs like
        Amanda Seyfried\'s can shorten long faces as effectively as a pert bob. "You're covering the area between your hairline and brow, removing several inches from your face," says Garren. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        Keep fine hair shoulder-length and flighty bangs centered by blow-drying. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        You can easily create old-fashioned waves like Seyfried\'s with a large-barrel curling iron, a paddle brush
        , and hair pins. Curl, gently brush, and pin back the sides to get the look.
    </string>

    <string name="heart_short">
        THE CUT \n
        A coy pixie that’s clipped evenly on the sides and nape with short layers on top. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Halle Berry’s tousled cut is dynamic enough to cancel out a pronounced jawline, while the choppy layers break up a wide forehead. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        Corkscrew curls and cropped hair don’t mix. To avoid a top-heavy effect that will exaggerate your chin, dense strands need
        to be sliced into. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        To extend the life of your whispy pixie do, try Living Proof Prime Style Extender. It\'s weightless so that
        your strands stay upright and ensures your style will last up to two times longer.
    </string>

    <string name="heart_medium">
        THE CUT \n
        A collarbone-length crop with sweeping bangs and uniform layers. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Actress Scarlett Johansson looks radiant with her short, choppy bob. This hairstyle is all about texture –
        cast aside your heat styling tools and your hair-taming products and embrace the fuzz! When going short make sure you get your
        hair cut by a stylist you trust to avoid hair mishaps and unnecessary tears. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        This is perfect for hair that has some body, but not the coarse or curly variety. "You\'ll get too much volume up top," says Johansson. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        For a full-bodied look like Johansson\'s, we swear by the GHD Air Hair Dryer. It\'s powerful enough to cut down on drying
        time while leaving hair soft, shiny and frizz-free.
    </string>

    <string name="heart_long">
        THE CUT \n
        Long hair with longer layers or fringe. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        The unofficial heart-shaped face ambassador, Reese Witherspoon, shows off yet another
        stunning hairstyle. Here she sports long, wavy hair with short angular bangs. Angular bangs work well to create the
        illusion of a longer face, and they give your haircut a modern edge. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        This look is easy to pull off, regardless of texture. If your hair is on the fine or sparse side, keep the layers long
        and concentrated closer to the ends. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Keep things wispy like Witherspoon and go for a texturizing spray or let your hair air-dry.
    </string>

    <string name="square_short">
        THE CUT \n
        A short layered bob with subtle bangs. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Troian Bellisario\'s cut brings the focus higher and puts the emphasis on your cheekbones, rather than your jaw. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        Dense strands could puff out at this length, so be sure to tame any frizzy pieces with a quick pass of a flat iron. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Here, Bellisario kept her short hairstyle and cut fairly au naturel and maintenance free—except for her platinum color.
        To subtly touch up roots from home—witthout having to see a colorist—try Madison Reed Root Touch Up. \n
    </string>

    <string name="square_medium">
        THE CUT \n
        Light shoulder-length layers all around that start a few inches above the ends with sweeping bangs. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Feathery layers (which can be achieved with a razor) like Lucy Hale\'s camouflage a strong chin. "The airy ends prevent the eye from noticing any sharp corners," says Garren. He recommends parting at the side for an asymmetrical effect, which
        also offsets squareness. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        The layers pump up any hair type. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        Even if you don\'t have wavy texture like Hale\'s, you can still get that naturally texturized look with DevaCurl Wave Maker. \n
    </string>

    <string name="square_long">
        THE CUT \n
        Collarbone-skimming strands with slight bangs that hit at the cheekbone. \n
        \n
        WHY IT WORKS \n
        Long locks are flattering, but you want to avoid a "simplistic" look with blunt ends, says Garren.
        There\'s nothing ho-hum or harsh about Shay Mitchell\'s structured ringlets. The airy fringe and light scattering of
        layers "get rid of angles and soften the entire face, top to bottom," says Garren. \n
        \n
        EXPERT TIP \n
        Keep layers to a minimum if your strands are fine. \n
        \n
        TO STYLE \n
        The Bio Iconic Curl Expert Pro Curling Iron works like a charm and this one with a 1" barrel will give you tight curls like Mitchell\'s.
    </string>
</resources>
